themegarden.com 2011-11-03

# Privacy Policy | ThemeGarden.com

This privacy policy covers the use of the web site located at http://www.themegarden.com and the services provided by Circa75 Media, LLC, including how ThemeGarden treats personal information that ThemeGarden collects and receives. Pursuant to ThemeGarden’s Terms of Use, you must be 18 years and older to use this site or have permission from a legal guardian. Therefore, this policy makes no provision for individuals under 18 years old. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that ThemeGarden does not own or control, or individuals that ThemeGarden does not employ or manage.

### Information Collection and How it is Used

ThemeGarden will not sell or disclose your name or email address to third parties without your explicit consent, except as specified in this privacy policy.  
Your username, ThemeGarden ID or alias is displayed throughout ThemeGarden (and so available to the public) and is connected to all of your ThemeGarden activity.ThemeGarden collects personal information when you register to use ThemeGarden services or to post content on ThemeGarden. At registration you are asked for your email address and certain other optional information. If you would like to obtain a Seller account, ThemeGarden will ask for your address and billing information. ThemeGarden automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookies, and the pages you request. This data is only used in the aggregate.

ThemeGarden uses information for products and services provisioning, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, research, and anonymous reporting. IP addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. Your IP address is stored in ThemeGarden’s user registration databases when you register with ThemeGarden. IP addresses may be used for various research purposes.

### Service-Related Announcements

ThemeGarden will send you a welcome/confirmation email when you sign up for ThemeGarden’s services. Receipt of this email is required for using ThemeGarden’s services. ThemeGarden will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. You may not opt-out of service-related communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account by emailing support@themegarden.com from the email address you signed up with.

### Administrative Messages

ThemeGarden may periodically email you with administrative messages. ThemeGarden will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Your information may be combined with information ThemeGarden collects from other companies and used to improve and personalize services, content and advertising. If you don’t wish to receive administrative messages or participate in these programs, simply opt-out by emailing support@themegarden.com.

### Newsletter Emails

ThemeGarden offers subscriptions to ThemeGarden email newsletters. To opt-in, ThemeGarden will ask for your email address and the newsletter(s) you wish to receive. This email address will only be used for this feature. You may change your subscription or unsubscribe at anytime by following the instructions contained in the email.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use ThemeGarden products or services that require you to “sign in,” and you may not be able to take full advantage of the ThemeGarden service. ThemeGarden uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to: Access your information when you “sign in”; keep track of preferences you specify while you are using ThemeGarden’s services; estimate and report ThemeGarden’s total audience size and traffic; conduct research to improve ThemeGarden’s content and services. ThemeGarden cookies do not collect personal information, and ThemeGarden does not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your username or email address is.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

ThemeGarden may disclose personally identifiable information to parties in compliance with ThemeGarden’s Copyright and Intellectual Property Policy, as ThemeGarden in ThemeGarden’s sole discretion believes necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. In such events, ThemeGarden may disclose name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email address and company name. ThemeGarden may share aggregated demographic information with business partners.

ThemeGarden is affiliated with a variety of businesses and works closely with them. These businesses may operate stores on the ThemeGarden website or sell items to you from the ThemeGarden website. ThemeGarden may also provide services or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses. Due to the nature of ThemeGarden’s business model, when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, you will share customer information that is related to such transaction with that affiliated business.

ThemeGarden will not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with nonaffiliated parties except as specified in this Privacy Policy to provide products or services you have requested or when ThemeGarden has your permission. It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of ThemeGarden’s Terms of Use, as specified in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise required by law. In some cases, ThemeGarden may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. ThemeGarden will transfer information about you if ThemeGarden is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, ThemeGarden will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the ThemeGarden web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and ThemeGarden’s ability to keep the community free from bad actors, ThemeGarden will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order, legal process, or substantially similar legal procedure, except when ThemeGarden believes in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to protect ThemeGarden’s rights, prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss, or to report suspected illegal activity.

### Forums / Chat Rooms

If you use a forum or chat room on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by others or could be used to send you unsolicited messages. ThemeGarden is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

### Third Parties

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information ThemeGarden collects from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether they are buyers or sellers on ThemeGarden or throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. ThemeGarden does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. ThemeGarden is not responsible for the privacy or security practices of other websites on the Internet, even those linked to or from the ThemeGarden site. ThemeGarden encourages you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

### Editing and Deleting Account Information

ThemeGarden may send you certain communications relating to the ThemeGarden service, such as service-related announcements and administrative messages that are considered part of your ThemeGarden account. You can delete your ThemeGarden account by emailing support@themegarden.com. Please note that your identification, billing and contact information may remain in ThemeGarden’s records for some period.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. Your ThemeGarden account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by signing off once you have finished using a shared computer. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) for registration ThemeGarden encrypts that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). ThemeGarden follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once ThemeGarden receives it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while ThemeGarden strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, ThemeGarden cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on ThemeGarden’s Web site, you can email ThemeGarden at support@themegarden.com.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

If the privacy policy is changed, ThemeGarden will post changes so that you are aware of those changes. ThemeGarden reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If ThemeGarden makes material changes to this policy you will be notified here, by email, or other places ThemeGarden deems appropriate.
